Time for a timeline cleanse.
Let's take it back to when I was in Belize with my homegirl, Janice, having a fabulous time.
So I stayed at Itzana down in Placencia, and the decor was majestic.
Then we head outside, and they put the same energy into the pool and the landscaping.
Oh, look at her. Fabulous.
Look at this fish!
Everyone loves coconut water in an actual coconut.
And you know what else we love?
Rest and relaxation.
See, in the constant fight that we're in right now, you've got to still find time to take your joy when you can.
And for me, it's to be by the ocean and with the sea.
So here's the room that we stayed in.
Walk up these stairs, and you know what?
Let's just head on outside.
Yes, buddy!
Yeah!
Nothing like a Belizean sunset.
I always say the sky is bigger here.
If you get a chance, you should see it too.